let questions=[   // It
{ numb :1 ,
question:"What is the process at the most detailed level of the data flow diagrams known as?",
answer:"functional primitives",
options:[
"Interfaces",
"functional primitives",
"data flow",
"none"
]
},
{ numb :2 ,
question:"Total bits used by the IPv6 address is ________  ",
answer:"128bit",
options:[
"64bit",
"256bit",
"128bit",
"32bit"
]
},
{ numb : 3,
question:"Identify the language which is mainly used for Artificial Intelligence",
answer:"Prolog",
options:[
"Java",
"J2EE",
"Prolog",
"C"
]
},
{ numb : 4,
question:"Why is a firewall used in a computer?",
answer:"Security",
options:[
"Security",
"database",
"Monitoring",
"Ai"
]
},
{ numb : 5,
question:"How many levels are there in the architecture of the database?",
answer:"3",
options:[
"2",
"3",
"4",
"5"
]
},
{ numb : 6,
question:"Among the following which is not a database management software",
answer:"COBOL",
options:[
"MYSQL",
"COBOL",
"Sybase",
"Oracle"
]
},
{ numb : 7,
question:"Identify the total standard color names that HTML supports.",
answer:"140",
options:[
"30",
"70",
"140",
"120"
]
},
{ numb :8 ,
question:"Choose the port number of FTP.",
answer:"21",
options:[
"23",
"21",
"110",
"143"
]
},
{ numb :9 ,
question:"Total number of layers in OSI model is ___________",
answer:"7",
options:[
"5",
"7",
"9",
"11"
]
},
{ numb : 10,
question:"UNIX is written in which language?",
answer:"C",
options:[
"C# ",
"C++",
"C",
"Php"
]
},
];